module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'Who created "Beavis and Butt-Head" and "King of the Hill"?', 
    a: 'Mike Judge',
    b: 'Matt Groening',
    c: 'Seth MacFarlane',
    d: 'Stephen Hillenburg',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: '"Zorro" is Spanish for what?', 
    a: 'Tiger',
    b: 'Fox',
    c: 'Phantom',
    d: 'Hero',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who is the main character in the video game series "Metroid"?', 
    a: 'Simon Belmont',
    b: 'Mega Man',
    c: 'Captain Falcon',
    d: 'Samas Aran',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Where is Mount Vesuvius located?', 
    a: 'Egypt',
    b: 'Greece',
    c: 'Italy',
    d: 'Nepal',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'What company\'s products were originally developed for laboratory use?', 
    a: 'Coleman',
    b: 'Nalgene',
    c: 'YETI',
    d: 'Igloo',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who was the widely criticized head of FEMA during Hurricane Katrina?', 
    a: 'Michael Brown',
    b: 'Brock Long',
    c: 'Craig Fugate',
    d: 'John Macy',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which city is known as the "Biggest Little City in the World"?', 
    a: 'Reno',
    b: 'Las Vegas',
    c: 'Tuscon',
    d: 'Salt Lake City',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Ewoks are native to which location?', 
    a: 'Endor',
    b: 'Tatooine',
    c: 'Alderaan',
    d: 'Zebes',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which actor is famous for playing the role of Count Dracula?', 
    a: 'Vincent Price',
    b: 'Christopher Lee',
    c: 'Lon Chaney',
    d: 'Boris Karloff',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which political commentator had once co-hosted CNN\'s "Crossfire" and now headlines their own show on Fox News?', 
    a: 'Bill O\'Reilly',
    b: 'Glenn Beck',
    c: 'Megyn Kelly',
    d: 'Tucker Carlson',
    answer: 'd'
  },
];